http://www.avirex.com/pages/terms-conditions

Terms + Conditions of Use
The term “AVIREX” includes the terms “CENTRIC CANADA APPAREL AND ACCESSORIES ULC” for the territory of Canada and "CENTRIC DENIM USA LLC" for the territory of the Unites States of America.
1. USE OF THE AVIREX SITE
This site is owned by Avirex and is operated for your personal use and information. Use of this site is governed by the terms and conditions outlined below and all applicable laws. By accessing and browsing this site, you confirm having read and understood these terms and conditions and accept them without limitation or qualification. Avirex may amend these terms and conditions at any time.
2. ACCESSING THE SITE
Avirex may monitor access to this site and other activities.
Avirex entirely adheres to the principles of human rights and freedoms and does not tolerate any form of discrimination based on race, national or ethnic origin, color, religion, sex, age, or mental or physical disability. Avirex reserves the right to terminate your access to all or any part of this site, with or without notice.
3. TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF SALE
When you purchase products using the www.Avirex.com site, your purchase is subject to separate Terms and Conditions of Sale which we invite you to consult:
All returns of products are governed by our Return Policy, which we also invite you to consult
Notwithstanding the foregoing
The present provisions shall supersede and take precedence over the provisions of the Terms and Conditions of Sale and the Return Policy;
In the event of any inconsistency, the present provisions shall govern.
4. PROTECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
Our privacy practices are explained in our Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site implies that you acknowledge that you have read our Privacy Policy and agree to be bound by and accept its terms and conditions. You consent to the use of your personal information by Avirex in accordance with the terms of and for the purposes set forth in our Privacy Policy.
Terms + Conditions of Sale
The term “AVIREX” includes the terms “CENTRIC CANADA APPAREL AND ACCESSORIES ULC” for the territory of Canada and "CENTRIC DENIM USA LLC" for the territory of the Unites States of America.
1. USE OF THE AVIREX SITE
This site is owned by Avirex and is operated for your personal use and information. Use of this site is governed by the terms and conditions outlined below and all applicable laws. By accessing and browsing this site, you confirm having read and understood these terms and conditions and accept them without limitation or qualification. Avirex may amend these terms and conditions at any time.
2. ACCESSING THE SITE
Avirex may monitor access to this site and other activities.Avirex entirely adheres to the principles of human rights and freedoms and does not tolerate any form of discrimination based on race, national or ethnic origin, color, religion, sex, age, or mental or physical disability. Avirex reserves the right to terminate your access to all or any part of this site, with or without notice.
3. TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF SALE
When you purchase products using the www.Avirex.com site, your purchase is subject to separate Terms and Conditions of Sale which we invite you to consult:
All returns of products are governed by our Return Policy, which we also invite you to consult
Notwithstanding the foregoing
The present provisions shall supersede and take precedence over the provisions of the Terms and Conditions of Sale and the Return Policy;
In the event of any inconsistency, the present provisions shall govern.
4. PROTECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
Our privacy practices are explained in our Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site implies that you acknowledge that you have read our Privacy Policy and agree to be bound by and accept its terms and conditions. You consent to the use of your personal information by Avirex in accordance with the terms of and for the purposes set forth in our Privacy Policy.
Back to Top
We Want You
Get updates, deals, and exclusive products direct to your inbox.
